They're chasing us!
We can't continue the concert on Lancaster any longer!
What?!
But this is our first concert!
Everyone is waiting for us.
Even if it kills us, we'll keep—
You should not speak of death so lightly.
But...
But if we leave Lancaster now,
doesn't that mean it'll become a planet with a total entertainment ban?
She's right!
If we retreat from Lancaster now,
we may never be able to go back again!
We can't go back.
I'll never see them again.
No.
Unacceptable!
Arne!
We haven't given the people of Lancaster anything at all yet!
She's right!
And besides,
I wanted...
I wanted my family and Mamoru to see our concert!
Mm-hmm.
In any case,
we'll be meeting up with Karayusha.
Subasa-san!
Docking with Katayusha complete.
We've broken away from our pursuers.
Keep an eye on the surrounding space, please.
Understood.
I don't want to make them abandon their home planet either.
But what can I do?
Mariko!
Mariko, you're so easily frightened!
No, I just don't see a reason to do this, A-chan.
I don't want to make them abandon their home planet, either.
But what can I do?
Mariko.
Mariko, you're so easily frightened.
No, I just don't see a reason to do this, Ah-chan.
A reason?
Not even the Woda are on this planet to help protect us.
There's no one waiting for us.
Is there any reason for us to go?
I see.
It's a little different for me.
Huh?
You've got it all wrong, Mariko.
I don't go because someone is waiting for me.
It's about them.
The reason I go is because I want to see everyone.
Ah-chan.
What should I do?
I was so surprised.
I know the DES hate us.
I know they're our enemy.
But...
They said they hated us with such frightening expressions.
It really scared me.
Sonata.
I thought Zero-Zero was all smiles and happiness.
I thought we were full of love.
I really did.
Mom?
It's true.
Zero-Zero is full of love.
It doesn't make sense that they hate us.
The DES are the bad ones.
You should never be ashamed of yourself, Sonati.
Huh?
Suzuko's angry.
I always wanted to return to Lancaster.
Chiri?
I couldn't forget.
The summer we spent together.
When we were little children.
I thought about returning to Lancaster again and again.
I want...
I want to perform on Lancaster.
Not just for someone else.
But also for myself.
Where are you going?
You go.
Are you going to negotiate directly
for the trainee concert on Lancaster?
You can't reach out to them.
It just won't work.
There's no point if they don't rise up themselves.
But...
I'll go with you.
What?
After all,
you still mean to hand over the name
Takamina to Kaneda soon, don't you?
Come on.
Let's send you out in style.
Make this thing a big bang.
We can do this right.
You go.
You want to see everyone, do you?
Yes.
For that reason.
I open the door.
Tsubasa-san!
You girls!
You have to let us resume the training concert on Lancaster.
It's too dangerous.
You'll be captured.
We want to go see them.
Please, Tsubasa, we're begging you!
Please, please!
What's going on?
I don't know.
They want to deliver it to them.
Ak-chan.
They want to deliver it.
You want to go see them?
What?
Is that Ak-chan's voice?
You want to deliver your feelings to them?
It's Ak-chan!
We want to go!
We want to deliver our feelings to them.
So do we!
Please let us!
What's going on?
The Kanata Drives Field is reaching the surface, ma'am.
Ak-chan?
Is this your doing?
Let's deliver it to them with your lights.
Illuminate everyone!
Calm down, everyone.
Start!
That light!
The Kanata's glowing!
Head toward the light, everyone!
If you want to see Zero Zero perform, run toward that light
as fast as you can.
Everybody go!
Wait, stop!
Ak-chan, you've always illuminated our path for us.
And you're doing it again.
Please be with us.
Let's go, everyone! Let's get this party started!
What is that?
Is that music?
A concert at the detention center? This is crazy!
But you gotta admit, it's the best place to perform if they're trying to liberate entertainment.
This is great! This is why I can't quit the WOTA!
Leader?
Yeah?
Why don't we take it all the way?
Ha! Of course!
That's it! Run as fast as you can! Shout as loud as you can!
We're back, everyone!
haczt it?
It's beautiful.
Let's go, guys.
Can't wait for David to come forcare,ursuit!
www.caphor報.com
That party's so 힘들う!
popin up!
It's dark and important…
Pri playoffs
repetcciones
形 cyclics
46-ером
The press Serie, dassel 果然
The machineента
Sanctuary 거
What's going on?
Zero-Zero?
Hey, everyone!
Why not listen to Zero-Zero's concert up close?
Stop!
Do you know what's going to happen to you?
You're Motomiya's father.
Yes.
And just who are you?
Let's go! Hurry!
Butch...
It's Nagisa-san's first concert!
You've got us here!
Nagisa, you should sing.
I didn't want...
All this time, I didn't want to lose to you.
But I realized it will never reach them if we keep fighting.
Everyone's waiting for you.
Deliver your feelings to the people of Lancaster.
Nagisa!
You're so cute!
Nagisa! Nagisa!
Nagisa!
Uh... Mom!
We're over here, too!
Nagisa!
Oh, Dad? Nagisa!
Okay, I'll sing!
We're over here!
No, Dad?
No!
Why?
Ittes affiliation, all right.
Ohinnen is no good!
Maybe!
There he was in or...
Thank you.
Sorry...
That sounds great!
...working.
Jelly, Jelly Boy, Jelly, Jelly Girl
Nagisa!
You're curious for me, too!
That's great! Her voice is finally back!
Uh-huh!
Nagisa!
Papa?
Come on, everyone!
We've still got the encore!
It's our new song!
Yeah!
Let's begin!
With our sweat and tears!
A new dream!
The new song!
Show them all you got!
Dead Light!
Yeah!
The character shone so brightly at Akchan's last concert.
Why?
It's not only Nakusa and Shea-ri.
Every one of the trainees is glowing.
Niki-sa, you're so wonderful.
This is good.
What's this?
Is everyone all right?
Yes.
No, Chiari!
What?
This is an important new song.
Let's leave the fighting to Takamina-san and the others.
Come on, now.
We'll assume a solid formation to evade the focus of their attacks, all right?
Kanata!
Roger, Captain.
Yeah, Captain!
Amazing.
Kanata really is the Takamina of the new generation.
Come on, everyone!
Let's make their stage shine as brightly as possible!
Takamina?
But don't forget, we're AKB-0048!
We deliver not war, but love!
She's singing it!
Don't move!
Yuko!
Takamina!
I'm fine!
It's just a scratch!
Kiraura!
Why is the holy place...
oh!
Oh, my God!
It domination remains!
Very dumb.
It is trying this transition.
She's singing it!
Dooku!
Youko, Takamina!
I'm fine.
It's… just a scratch.
eeee...
I'm fine.
It's… Just a scratch.
Her powerful love for the other members and her desire to make the concert a success resonated with the spirit of the original Minami Takahashi.
Minami Takahashi is Takamina.
Then what about Kaneda?
Centernova.
Centernova?
Could it be one of these girls?
bloodb Ona?
holiedenambo.
If you move your eyes,
Look at the heavens.
I like how this literally means more.
Who comes the moon.
biếtと 遠くにあるんだ
出雑な星だって 笑い声を 瞞しよう
おおー
Umm...
It's alright then!
Ohh...
Come on!
Kata-ro-ka
Yeah!
Ah!
Get down!
I'll protect them!
I'll do it!
Nagisa!
Ah!
Chiyari!
All right!
Ah!
Kira!
Coming through!
Amazing!
The mic sabers are more powerful than usual!
Launcher ready.
Feed systems ready.
Rapid fire.
You've been punished by my yuyu!
No!
Come on, everyone!
Leave this to us and go back to the concert!
Ugh!
Okay!
Kibou ni tsuite boku wa kata-roo
Nagisa!
We can feel it!
Our song and emotions are resonating!
And becoming one!
Hmph!
So this is entertainment!
Kibou ni tsuite boku wa kai-roo
Kibou ni tsuite boku wa cute
What's going on?!
Jons…
Thank you very much!
The Cendernovas...
Where are you now?
We barely made it this time.
But if one of those girls is going to become the next Cendernova,
I will finally discover its true meaning!
This glowing sand? Duelium?
Is that why the Cendernova phenomenon happened here?
Mom!
Mom! I missed you, Mom!
You were absolutely wonderful!
You really think so?
Yes!
Darling?
Oh, Dad...
I'm so sorry. I just...
Why are you apologizing?
Do you truly believe anything can be resolved if you simply apologize?
Is that all it meant to you?
Well, I...
A message for all members from the Acting Captain!
DES! Backup forces have appeared in the skies!
In order to avoid putting our fans in danger, we must retreat immediately!
What?
We're retreating already?
But I finally got to see you again!
I want you to go.
You already abandoned this planet once before, didn't you?
If you feel that strongly, you cannot stop!
Go forward and chase your dreams!
Oh, Dad!
See you later, Nagisa!
Thank you, Mama!
Thanks, Daddy!
Don't you turn back!
Go forward without turning back!
Dad... Mama...
Goodbye!
Nagisa!
Yeah!
Oh...
Mamoru!
Yuk...
Mom, I'm real...
Yuka.
I'm sorry.
But I...
I'm going now!
風の駅で待ってる日差し
空を渡る雲の線路
僕は時計をちらり眺めて
そっと深呼吸したんだ
君は行くなと引き止められてるのか?
愛を振り切れるか?
虹の列車が時刻通り
夢に向かって出発するよ
君と一緒に旅立ちたいんだ
全て捨ててやってこい
初音音に向かって出てみたい
だがたぶんが経つだ
だ district
You